<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">

    <!--<string name="lang_prompt">Choose a Language</string>
    <string-array name="lang_supported">
        <item>Choose your language</item>
        <item>Malayalam</item>
        <item>Hindi</item>
    </string-array>-->

   <!-- <string name="your_lang_prompt">Select your language</string>
    <string-array name="your_lang">
        <item>Select your language</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Malayalam</item>
        <item>Hindi</item>
    </string-array>-->
    <string name="About" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">
    Cadeceus is dedicated to changing people\'s lives through the power of language.
    The applications innovative digital solutions drive positive learning outcomes
    for the inspired learner at home or in schools and workplaces around the world.
    </string>
    <string name="text_with_paragraphs" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">

Il était une fois un oiseau qui aimait une baleine. Et une baleine qui aimait un oiseau.\n\n

Once upon a time there was a bird who loved a whale. And a whale who loved a bird.\n\n\n

L\’oiseau aimait le beau sourire de la baleine. Il aimait la façon gracieuse qu\’elle avait de nager dans l\’eau.
La baleine aimait les belles plumes blanches de l\’oiseau. Elle aimait le regarder planer dans le ciel.\n\n

The bird loved the whale\'s beautiful smile. He loved the gracious way she swam through the water.
The whale loved the bird\'s handsome white feathers. She loved to watch him soar through the sky.\n\n\n


Ils aimaient tous les deux manger beaucoup de petits poissons.\n\n

They both loved to eat lots of tiny fish.\n\n\n


Durant l\’été, l\’oiseau et la baleine se retrouvaient dans la baie. Ils parlaient beaucoup.
        Ils parlaient de la lune et des marées, et des bateaux sur l\’océan.\n\n

During the summer, the bird and the whale met in the bay. They talked a lot.
        They talked about the moon, and the tides, and the ships on the ocean.\n\n\n


L\’oiseau racontait des blagues et faisait rire la baleine. La baleine chantait de belles chansons qui faisaient pleurer l\’oiseau.\n\n

The bird told jokes and made the whale laugh. The whale sang beautiful songs that made the bird cry.\n\n\n

        Un jour, tu pourras rencontrer ma famille dans l\’océan », dit la baleine. \n\n
        Et tu pourras rencontrer mes amis sur terre », dit l\’oiseau. \n\n
        Tout était parfait.\n\n

                "One day, you can meet my family in the ocean," said the whale.\n\n
                "And you can meet my friends on the land," said the bird.\n\n
                Everything was perfect.\n\n\n


                Mais le monde ne s\’arrête pas de tourner simplement parce qu\’un oiseau et une baleine tombent amoureux.
                L\’été fit place à l\’automne et l\’automne fit place à l\’hiver. L\’océan devint froid et toutes les baleines partirent vers des eaux plus chaudes.\n\n

                But the world does not stop turning simply because a bird and whale fall in love. Summer gave way to autumn, and autumn gave way to winter.
                The ocean became cold, and all the whales left for warmer waters.\n\n\n


                « Viens avec moi vers des eaux plus chaudes », dit la baleine. « C\’est un endroit formidable.
                Il y fait toujours chaud et il y a tellement de poissons à manger. »\n\n

                "Come with me to warmer waters," said the whale. "It\’s a wonderful place. It always does warm there, and there are so many fish to eat."\n\n\n


                « J\’aime manger du poisson », dit l\’oiseau. « Et je t\’aime aussi. Je te suivrai n\’importe où. Mais d\’abord, apprends-moi à être une baleine. »\n\n

                "I love to eat fish," said the bird. "And I love you too. I will follow you anywhere. But first, teach me to be a whale."\n\n\n

                ""

    </string>

</resources>
